problogbooster.com 2018-08-20

# Privacy Policy Statement | ProBlogBooster

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/problogbooster.com).  

This **Privacy Policy Statement** is valid from 9th September 2009.   
This is a website created with BlogSpot blogging platform.   
Title: **ProBlogBooster - For Bloggers, By ProBloggers**   
Short Description: ProBlogBooster publishes software tips, blogging tips, how-to guides, SEO, making money online, affiliate marketing, mobile app reviews, and tutorials.   
Web link: [//www.problogbooster.com/](https://www.problogbooster.com/)  
Address: Rajarampuri, Kolhapur, India 

If you want any more information or have any queries about our privacy policy, please feel free to reach us by visiting [CONTACT US](https://www.problogbooster.com/2008/10/contact-me.html) page or you can email at [[email protected]](https://www.problogbooster.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#84f7f1f4f4ebf6f0c4f4f6ebe6e8ebe3e6ebebf7f0e1f6aae7ebe9)

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name along with IP addresses. 

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address and IP addresses. 

---  
Privacy Policy Statement ProBlogBooster  
  
Also check: [**Stuff I Wrote Before Today - Archives Pages**](https://www.problogbooster.com/2007/09/archives.html)

###  ProBlogBooster | Privacy Policy Statement

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Website. 

**With respect to cookies:** We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by visiting us at [Contact Me](https://www.problogbooster.com/2008/10/contact-me.html). 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by visiting us at [Contact Me](https://www.problogbooster.com/2008/10/contact-me.html). 

**With respect to Ad Servers:** This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of: 

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion, and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content. 

The owner of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers' own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question. 

From time to time, we may use visitors/readers, information for distinct & upcoming, unanticipated uses not earlier disclosed in our privacy notice. If collected data or information practices changed or improved at some time in the future, we would post all the policy changes to our Website to notify you of these changes, and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back our website Policy pages periodically. 

Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to no information that we have collected and that we maintain about them.   
Upon request, we offer visitors no ability to have factual inaccuracies corrected in information that we maintain about them 

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

#### FINAL WORDS: 

Any actions and or activities related to the material contained on this Website are solely your responsibility. The misuse of the information on this website can result in criminal charges brought against the persons in question. The owner will not be responsible in the event any criminal charges be brought against any individuals misusing the information in this blog to break the law. This blog contains materials that can be potentially damaging or dangerous. If you do not fully understand something on this site, then GO OUT OF HERE! Refer to the laws in your province/country before accessing, using, or in any other way utilizing these materials. These materials are for educational and research purposes only. Do not attempt to violate the law with anything contained here. If this is your intention, then LEAVE NOW! Neither administration of this server, the owner of this material, or anyone else affiliated in any way, is going to accept responsibility for your actions. Neither the owner nor blogger is responsible for the comments posted on this blog. This blog will never harm you by giving Out Trojans, Virus or any related stuff. We do not Promote Hacking! But lets one be aware of all the Possibilities around & promotes the way to curb it to protect you. 

Rest is [**ProBlogBooster** — For Bloggers, By ProBloggers](https://www.problogbooster.com/)

Adversal Media, Inc.  
(<https://www.adversal.com/online-privacy.html>) 

#### You liked this article? Please, share this...

Seriously. It helps a lot with the growth of this blog.   
Most of the online readers don’t share this article as they feels that we as bloggers don’t require their “tiny” social share. But here’s the fact…   
I've developed this blog piece by piece, your one small share at a time, and will continue encouraging me to do so. So I appreciate your support, my dear reader if you share this page on your social profile.   
It won’t take more than 5 seconds of your time. The share buttons are right here. 

#### Authorised by: __

A cybercrime expert, CBI - he is a personal technology columnist & the founder of ProBlogBooster. You can [follow him](https://plus.google.com/108768620429702103406) on the social media or subscribe the [email newsletter](https://feeds.feedburner.com/problogbooster) for your updated guides and tutorials. He talks about computer security and mostly publishes news articles about blogging tips, SEO, making money online, affiliate marketing, & reviews.

######  __Disclaimer

We are one of the type of a professional review site that operate like any other website on the internet. We respect & trust our readers. And we are confident & would like to mention that the above post contains some affiliate/referral links. And if you make a purchase; we receive commission from the links/apps/products we refer. We are totally unbiased and do not accept paid reviews or fake reviews claiming to be something they are not. We test each product thoroughly and give high marks to only the very best. We are independently owned and the opinions expressed here are our own. 

#### Get Latest Updated Post Directly Delivered to Your Inbox

Join over 2000+ people who get FREE and fresh content from this Blog. We Respect Privacy, You are Safe! No Spam!

[PBB2019]
